女士 抱歉打扰了
Excuse me, ma'am?
女士吗
Ma'am?
看来真要发生了
Well, it happened.
我要痛打小孩
I'm gonna hit a kid.
您愿意支持我们
Would you like to support my baseball league
贫困孩童棒球联盟吗
for underprivileged youth?
我并没有看到一个贫困孩童
I don't see an underprivileged youth.
我只看到一个年轻版的我 想骗老人版的我
I see a young me trying to scam an old me.
先生
Sir?
抱歉 我有糖尿病
I'm sorry, I have diabetes.
而且我不是傻逼
And I'm not stupid.
一边去
Move it along.
这不是在骗钱
It's not a scam!
我跟小伙伴们只想要下课后
My friends and I just want to place
能有场地打棒球
to play baseball after school
不想像玩饶舌的人一样 在街上游荡
so we're not hanging on the streets like rap people.
孩子 卖糖诈骗术是我发明的
Kid, I started the candy scam.
我募了500元给流浪汉保龄球联盟
I raised $500 for a homeless bowling league,
又名 大麻
AKA pot.
接住 棒球男孩
Catch this, Mr. Baseball.
别扔脸
Not the face!
我知道你是哪一队的了
I think I know which team you play on,
不是棒球队 是小受队
and it ain't baseball.
你还在你的手机上当剁手党乱买吗
You still shopping on your phone for things you can't afford?
你是谁啊 美国所有民众吗
Who are you? Everyone in America?
我只是把东西加进购物车 不买
I just add things to my cart without buying them.
一块苹果手表在手 不如两块在购物车
Why not buy one Apple watch when I can not buy two?
这叫过干瘾
It's called dry shopping.
就类似"干磨蹭" 只是你啥都捞不着吗
So it's like dry humping, but you don't get anything?
别说我嘛 麦克斯
I'm sorry, Max,
明天是我失去万贯家财
but tomorrow's the anniversary of when I lost my money
与桃红加奶白肤色的纪念日
and my peaches-and-cream complexion.
不是我自夸 是少女杂志《17》写的
Not my words; "Seventeen" magazine's.
我需要一个幻想的生活
I need a fantasy life.
我只是以为你早放下那些陈年屁事了
I mean, I just thought you were over all that junk.
你以为我已"放下"失去50亿
You thought I was "over" losing $5 billion
与原有人生这事了吗
and my whole life?
可能只是我已习惯你说不停这事了吧
I guess I was just over you talking about it all the time.
你得抛开你的过去
You need to let go of your past.
上菜 火鸡汉堡...吧
Pickup! Turkey burger... ish.
要不是你忙着"不买"
If you weren't so busy not buying a...
一间在上东区的三房别墅
three-bedroom townhouse on the Upper East Side,
你就会发现十号桌的火鸡汉堡哥
you would've noticed that Mr. Turkey Burger at table ten's
在打量你的翘臀呢
been checking out your buns.
才没有呢 他真看了吗
He is not. He is?
赶紧上吧
Get in there.
性爱还是免费的
Sex is still free...
至少女人不要钱
For women.
好吧 我现在过去
Fine, I'll go over there,
但这最好不是在整人
but this better not be a prank,
就像上次你跟我说杰出女演员在第十桌
like when you told me Bette Midler was at table three
而且超级想见我
and really wanted to meet me.
结果只是某个犹太老太婆
It was just some old Jewish lady,
而且她人超坏
and she was mean.
真的是贝蒂·米勒她本人啊
That was Bette Midler!
这是你的火鸡汉堡
Here's your turkey burger.
我朋友觉得你在勾搭我
My friend thinks you're flirting with me,
但很显然你并没有
and you're obviously not,
能不能麻烦你告诉她你没这想法
so if you could just tell her you're not,
我会很感谢你
that'd be great.
好吧
Okay.
我会告诉她我没有在勾搭你
I will tell her I am not flirting with you...
但有个条件
on one condition.
你明天晚上跟我去看场表演
You go see a show with me tomorrow.
你好坏坏
I feel tricked.
所以... 你答应吗
So... is that a yes?
希望是答应
I hope so,
因为我已经把我号码写下来了
because I already wrote down my number.
好啊 可以
Um... yeah, sure.
如果你都已经写下来了
I mean, if it's already written down,
我不去也不行啊
I guess I have to go.
真不敢相信我没发现他在勾搭我
I can't believe I didn't notice he was flirting.
我是哪里有毛病啊
What's wrong with me?
让我拿出你的《毛病大全集》
Let me get my list.
大家安安
Hi, everybody!
好消息宣布
Good news!
我跟奥列格决定找一个代理孕母
Oleg and I are getting a surrogate to carry our baby.
另一种怀孕方式花太久时间了
Yeah, doing it the other way was taking longer
比我结巴的叔叔说完一句话还久
than my stuttering uncle did to finish his s-s-s-sentence.
苏菲 希望你不是打算找我当代理孕母
Sophie, I hope you're not thinking of me to be your surrogate.
你别忘了
Just keep in mind,
你连包包都不准我"代"你拿
you won't even let me carry your purse.
你觉得我会请一个比我还老的代理孕母吗
You think I'd hire a surrogate that's older than me?
别闹了 当然不是
Come on. No.
麦克斯这周会帮我在我的卡座面试孕母
Max is helping me interview people this week in my booth.
好兴奋啊
This is so exciting.
我希望我能选自己在谁肚子里长大
I wish I got to pick the person I grew inside.
我妈妈在怀孕时喝太多酒
My mom drank so much during her pregnancy,
我出生时就穿着酒鬼招牌衣服
I was born wearing a shirt that says,
写着"世上某处已到喝酒点"
"It's 5:00 somewhere."
咱们能承认抽电子烟也算抽烟吗
Can we all just admit vaping is smoking?
总之 我在这不知道啥玩意的宾客列表上
Anyway, I'm on the list for whatever this is.
钱宁 卡洛琳
Channing, Caroline.
看到了 表演收费20块钱
There you are. The show's $20.
我的对象把我加进了名单
My date put me on the list.
我挺确定他帮我付了票钱
I'm sure he paid for me.
他追我追地挺殷勤
He kind of pursued me pretty hard.
毕竟怎么说 这也是场约会
It is, again, a date.
那看来你在跟废柴交往
Well, then you're dating a loser...
而且你还欠我20块钱
and you owe me 20 bucks.
那我仅剩的20块是花在什么上呢
What am I spending my last $20 on right now?
是一个说故事秀
It's a storytelling show.
人们诉说他们个人的故事
People telling their personal stories.
基本上就是个有趣的方式
It's basically a fun way to find out
来知道你的哪个朋友有一个继父
which one of your friends had a stepfather
坏到不行
that was so mean.
你这里接受以卫生巾代替钱吗
In lieu of cash, would you accept a tampon?
我有量少型 普通型 量多型
I have light, regular, super.
全都是让你能舒适度过经期的好货
Everything you don't feel on your period.
我的经痛一点都不好玩好吗
There is nothing funny about my cramps.
我每个月有三天都下不了床
I don't get out of bed three days a month.
我去打给我朋友吧
I'll go call a friend.
所以这会我已经上高中了
So by now I was in high school.
但当我以为我已经逃离恶霸时
But just when I thought I'd escaped my bullies,
我遇到了最坏的一个 青春期
I met the worst one yet: puberty.
额滴神啊
Oh, God.
麦克斯 谢谢你带20块来救急
Thanks for bringing the $20, Max,
也对不起 害你得多花20块
and sorry you had to spend another $20.
还挺合理 我在我爹骗光全城纪念日时
It figures, on the anniversary of my father stealing money,
被别人给骗了钱
I get ripped off by another guy.
老娘绝对要把40块捞回来
Well, I'm getting that $40 back.
我今晚花的钱 比2013一整年还多
I spent more money tonight than I did in 2013.
当时是我高中的一场舞会
It was a high school dance,
瑞秋·穆尼 人见人爱的校花
and Rachel Mooney, a popular girl,
当众扒我裤子整我
pulled down my pants.
没错
That's right.
我被人跳舞扒裤恶整了
I got dance-pantsed.
这男的从汤姆·克鲁斯
Oh, this guy just went from Tom Cruise
变成汤姆·睡死死了
to Tom Snooze.
最后 我学到了
In the end, what I learned
我才是我人生这幅画的画家
is that I'm the painter of my life,
我可以把我不想看到的部分涂掉
and I can paint out what I don't want to see.
我的画笔由我操控
My brushes are mine.
每一笔刷都由我做主
My strokes are mine.
猜猜谁裤裆里的"画笔"今晚不会被"操"控
Guess what's not getting stroked tonight.
亚当老兄的"画笔"
Old Adam's paintbrush.
这鼓掌绝对是带讽刺性吧
That's got to be sarcastic applauding, right?
因为我觉得每一声掌声的尾音
'Cause I feel like I heard, like, a question mark
都带着问号
at the end of the clap.
谢谢 亚当·奥古斯特
Thank you, Adam August.
现在到了节目的尾声
That is the end of our show.
我想谢谢所有的表演者
I'd like to thank all of our performers.
活出你的人生 做你独家听众
You live the stories that we live to hear.
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
我知道 挺震撼挺真
I know, that was pretty real.
真得很又臭又长
It was real long.
所以我们去哪里吃晚饭
So where are we going for dinner?
你来请客 她一起来
Your treat, and she's coming.
我今晚情绪上已经耗光 累了
Actually, I'm pretty spent emotionally.
我们金钱上也耗了40块呢
Well, we're spent forty-dollars-ally.
今晚大概就是属于那种
It's just one of those nights where...
把一切都散尽在台上的夜晚
you leave it all on the stage.
你有没有刚好散几张20块在台上呢
You happen to leave a couple twenties up there?
让我把事情理一下
Let... let me get something straight.
你就聊几个恶霸 就情绪上筋疲力尽了吗
You gave all of yourself talking about a couple bullies?
你知道这根本算不上是艰苦人生吧
That's not a rough life. You know that, right?
我只知道我有权拥有人生遭遇
Well, I know I'm entitled to my truths
以及人生遭遇带给我的感受
and how my truths make me feel.
的确 但你又没有失去了几十亿
Yeah, but it's not like you lost a billion dollars
老爸去坐牢 而且还得当我的室友
and your father went to prison and you had to move in with me.
而我绝对比瑞秋·穆尼恶霸十万倍
And I am a way bigger bully than Rachel Mooney.
卡洛琳才有艰苦遭遇
Caroline has a rough story.
每个人的遭遇没有可比性
Again, we can't compare our truths.
抱歉 但你真的遭遇过那些事吗
I'm sorry, but did all that really happen to you?
你失去几十亿吗
You lost billions?
正是五年前的今天失去的
Five years ago today, in fact.
再加上今晚的损失 我失去了50亿又40元
And with what I lost tonight, $5 billion, $40.
你有考虑过
Well, have you ever considered
在一个安心的场合诉说你的故事吗
telling your story in a safe space?
你只指那些你能托养不想养的孩子
You mean one of those locations where you can drop off a baby,
又不会问你任何问题的地方吗
no questions asked?
不 不是
N... no. No.
我是指这里
No, I mean here.
在这里说你的故事
Telling your story here.
是这样的
Hey, you know what?
我估计有几个粉丝在外面等我
I probably have some fans waiting for me outside,
就让我还你自由
so I will leave you be.
你还在这里啊
You're still here?
谢谢您的邀请 但我不太算是编剧
Thanks for the offer, but I'm not really a writer.
也不是会来这里第二次的人
Or a person who would come here twice.
况且 我在试着放下这段过去
Plus, I'm trying to put my story behind me.
好吧 你再考虑考虑
All right. Well, think about it.
会有50块酬劳 这是我的名片
It pays $50. Here's my card.
你在汽车出租公司工作吗
You work at Avis?
那是我另一份工作
That's my other job.
记得 你有个该分享的故事
And remember, you have a story to tell.
还有 有时候短租一台车
And sometimes renting a car is actually cheaper
比长租还划算呢 所以...
than a long-term lease, so...
我觉得你应该来说啊
I think you should totally do this.
说出我的故事 得到解脱吗
To finally tell my story and give it closure?
算是吧 但主要是看在50块的份上
Yeah, a little of that, but mostly the 50 bucks.
我来参加代理孕母面试
I'm here for the surrogacy interview.
麦克斯 又来了一个孩子的妈
Max, we got another baby mama.
看看这些来"投怀送肚"的女人
Look at all these woman trying to get pregnant.
简直就像美国职篮全明星周末啊
It's like NBA All-Star Weekend.
这是我的简历 停车费报销吗
Here's my resume, and do you validate?
我从来没被报销过 你也别想
I've never been validated, so you're not getting validated.
我很惊叹你有车
But I am impressed you have a car,
你先请坐吧
so have a seat.
我在写表演要说的故事
Max, I've been working on my life story for the show.
"我从小就梦想着要当一名公主
"As a little girl, I dreamt of being a princess.
而一直到我失去了一切 我才意识到...
It wasn't until I lost everything that I realized...
我本来一直都是个公主"
that's what I'd already been."
还有别的吗
What else you got?
别这样 麦克斯 这很重要
Come on, Max, this is important.
我从来没有说过我失去家财的那一天
I've never told the story about the day I lost my money,
所以比较新鲜生涩
so it's all very raw.
但你要知道
Okay, but just know,
有时候有些事物会太过生
sometimes things can be too raw,
比如那天那个鸡肉招牌三明治
like that chicken club sandwich that
在桌上还鸡鸣了两声
buck-kaw'd at the table.
看来我去上
Looks like my appearance
布鲁克林小生意播客秀的辛苦
on the Brooklyn Small Business podcast
终于获得回报
really paid off!
傻孩子 这些不是顾客
These aren't customers, silly.
这些只是一群为了钱 啥都愿意做的女人
These are just women that will do literally anything for money.
她们有人愿意招呼顾客吗
Will any of them wait tables?
阿憨 我能去你办公室写作吗
Han, can I go work in your office?
我需要把我的人生故事写下来
I just need to write my life story.
我发誓我绝对不乱碰你的乐高玩具
I promise I won't play with your Legos.
你是说那些个保护他
You mean those little plastic men
一辈子不会失去贞操的塑料小人吗
protecting his virginity?
苏菲 准备好见下一个代理孕母候选人了吗
Sophie, ready to meet the next potential surrogate?
厕所第二隔间的女人出局了
Oh, well, the lady in stall two is out.
我刚才听到她的蛋蛋碰到水的声音
Yeah, I just heard her balls hit the water.
奥列格呢
Where is Oleg?
抱歉 我刚在看一个网络视频
Sorry, I was watching a YouTube video
学习怎么做意大利粉
on how to make spaghetti.
我以前做的真是大错特错啊
Boy, I was way off.
苏菲
Uh, Sophie?
这位是克蕾儿
This is Claire.
你很喜欢她用粉红色笔填的申请表
You liked that her application was filled out in pink pen.
你不介意我坐下吧
Do you mind if I sit down?
我的背要疼死了
My back is killing me.
你的肚子才要气死我呢
Yeah, well, your front is killing me.
你搞毛啊
I mean, what the hell?
我不知道你知不知道这事
I don't know if you're aware of this,
但你的"已占用"灯在亮呢
but your "No Vacancy" sign is flashing.
我知道 但在我把这"礼物"
Yes, but once I give this gift
送给特里贝克地区的那对同性夫妻后
to a lovely same-sex couple in Tribeca,
我很乐意帮你怀你们的"礼物"
I would love to carry your gift into the world.
我已经当过12次代理孕母了
I've been a surrogate 12 times.
你是啥啊
What are you?
宝宝糖果罐吗
A baby PEZ dispenser?
生12个之后能干嘛 免费换一个潜艇堡吗
What do you get after 12? A free sub?
下一个
Next!
怀孕12次吗
Pregnant 12 times?
下面两片肯定跟酒吧推门一样了吧
Must be like saloon doors down there.
我不知道了
I don't know.
你确定不愿意付超过200块的酬劳吗
Are you sure you can't spend more than $200 on this thing?
因为我觉得省钱的后果
Because I feel like it's reflecting
都反映在低品质报名者上了
in the pool of candidates.
哪件能表达这句话 "谁说在人生低谷
Which one says, "Just because I'm at my bottom
就不能穿漂亮上衣"
doesn't mean I can't wear a nice top"?
就连你的衣服都话太多
Even your shirts talk too much.
麦克斯 你能正经点吗
Max can you be serious?
不能 但我知道你能
No, but you sure can.
我看了你的故事 太正儿八经了
I read your story, and it is supes serious,
于是我擅自做主 插了几个笑话进去
so I took the liberty of putting some jokes in.
《辛德勒的名单》这部电影虽然很压抑
I mean, "Schindler's List" was depressing,
但至少里面也有笑话啊
but at least there were still jokes.
你修改了我的人生故事
You changed my life story?
这上面还沾上黄芥末了
You got mustard on my life story?
我加了一点即兴笑话 还吃了一根热狗
I added a few riffs and had a hot dog.
我觉得你的故事真的非常非常悲伤
I think your story is really, really sad,
人们会觉得很没劲
and it's gonna bum people out,
你也会觉得很扫兴
and that's gonna bum you out,
我就会觉得很烦躁
and that's gonna bum me out.
我对在音乐剧《卡米洛特》
Well, as I said to Mrs. Shearson,
指导我的希尔森先生也这么说
who directed me in "Cabaret,"
我不知道我该怎么变得更好
I don't know how I could be much better,
但我乐意接受你的意见
but I'm open to your ideas.
好了 让我听听你的笑料吧
All right, let me hear some of your funnies.
首先
All right, first of all,
我们让阿憨坐前排
we're gonna sit Han in the front row,
然后你就说
and you're gonna say,
"我就长话短说来配合这短小家伙吧"
"I'm gonna keep this short, 'cause this guy did."
然后暂停 迎接我预计五到十分钟的笑声
Hold for what I have to imagine is a five-to ten-minute laugh.
好了 第一部分结束后
Okay, all through this first section,
你的车径直驶入"呼噜镇"
you're driving right through Snoresville,
然后右转来到"没人在乎城"
and then you take a slight right into Who-gives-a-crap-town.
重点是 你开的是2016版的福特"无聊车"
The point is you're driving a 2016 Ford Bore-us.
好啦
All right, fine.
我会穿插一些你的笑话
I'll put some of your jokes in.
可我不想攻击安妮·海瑟薇
Oh, but I don't want to attack Anne Hathaway.
她受到的攻击还不够多吗
Hasn't she been through enough?
事已至此
And after it was all said and done,
我看着我的阴道
I looked at my vagina...
我的阴道也看着我
And my vagina looked at me,
那是彼此会意的眼神
and we shared a knowing glance.
仿佛她在示意 准许我诉说她的故事
It was as if she was giving me permission to tell her story.
谢谢 阴道妹
Thank you, vagina.
也感谢各位的聆听
And thank you for listening.
我从未想过会有我厌倦
I never thought I could get tired
听到"阴道"这个词的一天
of hearing the word "vagina,"
但今日似乎就是那天
and yet, here I am.
小费挺少的 对吧
Hey, tips are kind of low, huh?
你想不想挣200块 很可能是250块
How'd you like to make $200, possibly $250,
当我的代理孕母
to have my baby?
干嘛
What?
在哪儿打工不是打呀
You carry stuff anyway.
无所谓
Just as well.
我也不想我们宝宝的发色像她那样
I didn't want our baby to have that hair color.
那个女服务员去哪儿了
Where's that waitress going?
我要加倍
I need a double.
加倍啥
A double what?
啥都加倍
Double anything.
各位感觉怎么样
How's everyone doing out there?
来这里度过周五夜是不是很棒呀
Isn't this a wonderful way to spend a Friday night?
我是下一个上台
I'm up next.
按照9到10打分 我看起来多少分
On a scale of 9 to 10, how do I look?
你看起来很漂亮
You look beautiful,
所以当你开口讲笑话时
so they're gonna be really surprised
人们一定会相当惊喜
when you have jokes.
下一位故事讲述者是第一次登台
And our next storyteller is here for the first time,
一个史诗般的故事 仿佛由两个故事组成
reading a tale so epic that it should be two tales.
就像双尾梅露希娜
And like the two-tailed Melusina,
欧洲民间传说的蛇女
a serpent of European folklore...
她十分美艳动人
She is truly a beauty.
这家伙到底在说什么鬼呀
What in good God is that man talking about?
下面有请卡洛琳·钱宁
Please welcome Caroline Channing.
正如他所说 我的名字是卡洛琳·钱宁
As he said, my name is Caroline Channing.
那曾经有着特殊的意义
That used to mean something special,
而在过去的几年里我学到
and I have learned through the past few years
它依然如此
that it still does.
我的父亲是马丁·钱宁
My father was Martin Channing,
纽约最受人憎恨的男人
the most hated man in New York City.
排在有线电视修理工之后
Except for any Time Warner Cable guy...
算了 我不需要看稿
You know what? I don't need to look at this.
一切心中皆有数
I know what happened.
永远难以忘怀
I'll never forget it.
你不会忘记你迷失自我的那天
You don't forget the day that you lose yourself.
天啊
Oh, boy.
她脱稿了
She's off script.
玩自由发挥
She's gone rogue.
那个女服务员在哪里
Where's that waitress?
我要加倍他的加倍
Double his double!
我的司机带我驶过第五大道
As my driver drove down 5th Avenue
停在我的豪华别墅前
and up to my townhouse,
我看见外面停着一辆警车
I saw there was a police car parked out front.
一开始我想 "是来抓我的吗"
And at first, I thought, "Am I being arrested?"
在等红灯时 假唱卢达克里斯的歌
Lip-synching to Ludacris at a stoplight!
但被抓走的 是我的父亲
But it was my father being arrested.
我看见我父亲戴着手铐
I saw my father in handcuffs.
就在那一瞬间
There, in that instant,
我从公主变成了贫民
I went from princess to pariah.
她居然浪费了一个超级棒的
Well, she threw away a perfectly good
"贫民凯莉"笑话
"Pariah Carey" Joke.
我是在给她保驾护航好吗
Just looking out for my girl here.
我的完美世界瞬间坍塌
My perfect world was shattered.
我看见那个我曾信任的男人
I saw the man who I trusted,
全世界我最信任的男人
who I believed in more than anyone,
那个会给我念睡前故事
who read me bedtime stories
用童趣的方式教我系鞋带的男人
and taught me how to tie my shoes with bunny ears...
我看见我父亲戴着手铐
I saw my father in handcuffs.
他偷走了我的信任
He stole my trust,
我对人的信任
my belief in people,
我的单纯天真
my innocence.
如果她不说"纯洁[童贞]"这个词 我就走人了
If she doesn't say "virginity," I am leaving.
他偷走了那个我想象中的自己
He stole who I thought I was
让我去寻找 真正的自己
and left me to find who I really am.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
没反应吗
Nothing?
我们得偷偷把她弄到后门溜走
We got to sneak her out the back door.
你刚讲得又悲伤又成功
You were so sad and triumphant
而且还...
and... so...
我要飙泪了
Oh, here come the waterworks!
卡洛琳
Caroline,
你说过你永远不会这么做
I know you said you never would,
但你感动[摸]了我
but you touched me.
你的故事触动了我的心弦
That really tugged at my heartstrings...
或电线 管线
or cables or wires
反正是里面那个让我活着的东西
or whatever's in here keeping me alive.
卡洛琳
Caroline...
你知道我和你都需要什么吗
Oh, you know what you and I both need?
爱的抱抱
A hug. Yeah.
感觉很好吧
It's nice, isn't it?
卡洛琳 刚才太棒了
Caroline, that was great!
很高兴我能用我了不起的故事激励你
I'm so glad I inspired you with my awesome story.
你怎么还在这儿啊
You're still here?
抱歉我没有讲你的笑话 麦克斯
I'm sorry I didn't do your jokes, Max.
算了 你根本不需要
You know what? You didn't need them!
我觉得人们有时候喜欢悲伤
I think people sometimes like to be sad.
所以阿黛尔才这么红
That's why there's Adele.
我觉得我终于解脱了
I think I finally got closure.
过去了 麦克斯
It's gone, Max.
爱你
Love you.
爱你的故事
Love your story.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是妮娜·施皮格尔
I'm Nina Spiegel.
我觉得这故事引人入胜
I found the whole thing riveting.
起起落落 跌落谷底
The ups, the downs, the way-downs.
你的故事真是一应俱全
Ugh, your story had it all.
她不会跟你玩3P的
She's not joining your threesome.
抱歉 通常有女人夸我都是因为想玩3P
Sorry, that's usually what women want when they compliment me.
我想谈谈把这故事带去我的制片厂[公寓]
Look, I'd like to talk about taking this to my studio.
你还有自己的小公寓吗
You have your own studio apartment?
让欢呼继续
Let the wooing continue.
不 那是电影制片厂
No, it's a film studio.
华纳兄弟
Warner Brothers.
拍《大嘴怪》的那个华纳兄弟吗
The Tasmanian Devil Warner Brothers?
我觉得我们能将你的故事变成电影
I think we can turn your story into a movie.
真的吗
Really?
卡洛琳·钱宁传奇故事
The Caroline Channing story
理应能在大荧幕上
deserves to live on the big screen
存活一到两周
for one to two weeks.
然后永远待在电视点播里
Then On Demand for eternity.
老天
Oh, my God.
麦克斯 这太让人激动了
Max, isn't this exciting?
我知道
I know!
墨西哥飛毛腿鼠也是他们公司的
They have Speedy Gonzalez too!
我还在等 麦克斯
I'm still on hold, Max.
我知道妮娜是个大人物
I know Nina's important,
因为她的助手让我等了六次
because her assistant has put me on hold six times
静音了我两次
and muted me twice.
还可以静音你吗
Muting you's an option?
他们怎么不在你的说明书里写上
Why wouldn't they put that in your manual?
你好
Hi!
开什么玩笑
Oh, are you kidding?
我最爱等[端盘子]了
I love waiting.
苏菲 这是你的安慰汤圆
Sophie, here's your consolation gnocchi,
来"安慰"你没找到代孕妈妈
for not finding somebody to get gn-knocked up.
谢谢 奥列格
Oh, thanks, Oleg.
至少我还有你
Well, at least I have you.
算了 苏菲
You know what, Sophie?
我来帮你代孕吧
I'll be the surrogate,
但如果怀孕了 我奶涨到撞倒路灯
but if my pregnancy boobs knock over a street lamp,
那得算在你的保险账上
that's on your insurance.
谢谢你的好意 麦克斯
That's real nice of you, Max,
但如果说我从卡洛琳的故事学到什么的话
but if there's anything that I learned from Caroline's story,
就是不能放弃 即使到了应该放弃的地步
it's that you can't give up, even if you should.
所以你们要继续努力造人吗
Oh, so you're gonna keep trying?
不 我们要领养
No, we're gonna adopt,
我们会珍惜这个小宝宝
and we will cherish this little baby,
就算它不是我们亲生的
even if it's not technically from us.
对 奥列格说得对
Yeah, Oleg's right.
我有一半头发也不是我自己的
I mean, half my hair's not from me,
但我对它们视如己出 爱护有加
but I love it just as much as if it were.
他们要我飞去好莱坞
They are flying me to Hollywood!
他们想我坐头等舱
They want to bring me out first class
去参加见面会
for a meet-and-greet.
但我拒绝了
But I told them no.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
你不能拒绝见面会
You can't pass up a meet-and-greet.
你不能拒绝任何肉[谐音]
You can't pass up any kind of meat.
你贫血好吗
You're anemic.
我换成了两张经济舱机票
I switched the tickets for two coach seats.
我想你跟我一起去
I want you to come with me!
谁稀罕能平躺的座位
Who needs to lie flat
我只想跟我的闺蜜和一个胖犹太人
when I can be squished between my best friend
挤在飞机的36排
and an obese rabbi in row 36?
我们要去好莱坞啦
We're going to Hollywood!